Henry Arcangelo

Developer



Contact



+351 927 285 125



henry.arcangello@gmail.com



arcangelo.net



www.github.com/ARCANGEL0

R. João Vieira, 284 Rio Tinto/Porto - Portugal



linkedin.com/in/henryarcangelo

About Me

I am a backend developer with a degree in Systems Analysis and Development, experienced in NodeJS, PHP, Laravel, React, React Native, Python, Typescript, SQL and others,

Dedicated and persistent, I strive for continuous learning and professional growth. I seek opportunities to apply my technical skills, contribute to challenging projects, and join a collaborative, innovative team.

Skills

Language & Frameworks

Javascript ES6, PHP, Java, C#, Python, Typescript | Nodejs, Laravel, React & Native, Flask, Django, CakePHP, Redux, Next, Vue.js, Bootstrap, Spring boot

Databases

Oracle, MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLServer, Firebase, MongoDB

DevOps

Docker, CI/CD

Version control

Git, Gitlab

Management

Agile methodologies, Scrum, Kanban, Trello

o Design & Media

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Figma, CorelDraw, AfterEffects, Première, Lucidchart, DBDiagram, UML

O Soft skills Initiative, critical thinking, adaptability, attention to detail, conflict resolution, fast learner, punctual

Education

♦ Technician in Software Analysing & Development

Alberto Santos Dumont ETEC

2019 - 2021

In-depth exploration of software development methodologies, focusing on Agile practices and effective developer techniques. Delving into programming languages like Java, Python, and PHP. Examination of network architectures, software modeling, and MVC design concepts. Also, covering cybersecurity and software vulnerability analysis.

Certifications

- Graphical Design
- Web development
- Network architecture
- Administration
- Projects management & Agile development
- Web & Mobile fullstack
 (React, Next, SQL, Vue.js,
 Electron, Expo)
- CompTIA+ certifications

Experience

CS Agent

Concentrix

08/2024 - Present

Provided customer support to Booking.com partners, resolving Admin page problems and technical issues within partner management dashboard. Providing help in a business outsourcing environment, consistently maintaining high customer satisfaction.

Feeelance developer.

ARCANGEL0

01/2024 - 06/2024

Develop websites and web applications using various technologies, manage back-end services, create mobile apps, integrate APIs, and provide technical support while maintaining clear communication with clients.

Sales associate

Amatel Ltda.

03/2022 - 02/2023

Technical support and hardware maintenance Selling of hardware, computer peripherals, and security electronics.

Advising customers on product selection tailored to their needs.

Fullstack Developer

LNA Digital

05/2019 - 01/2022

Develop and maintain management systems, dashboards, and small ERP systems for small businesses.

Create digital media and establish digital brand presence for clients.

Design and develop responsive websites and mobile applications to optimize user experience and brand visibility.

♦ Instructor

Directional courses.

06/2018 - 02/2019

Instructing in web design with a focus on programming logic, JavaScript, and Object-Oriented Programming (OOP).

Instructing in digital design using Adobe Creative Suite for graphic design and multimedia creation.

Instructing on IT basics including operating systems, peripherals, networks, and system architecture.

Languages







